Hello, I'm Mayu Tamura from Nogizaka46
I'm Haruka Kaki. Lilia Ito. Renko Iwamoto.
We are now at Animal Japan 2024!
Oh yes!
Well, well, well... I think you all know that we are the cheering fans.
I'd like to visit various booths now.
see you later
It's not fair. I'm caught between these two colors.
what to do
I'm your personal knight.
We have two cameras, so everyone gets a full shot.
Isn't it amazing?
May I show you something?
Not all of them?
amazing (e.g. of strength)
Hot Stir?
The heat is off. The heat is off.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
Great, great, great, great, great!
clattering noise
mushroom
yay
Isn't it cool?
I'm invincible.
"cool
Together?
soon
amazing (e.g. of strength, effort, etc.)
Looks strong Looks strong
This is Lilia's
My voice with Lilia as a voice actor.
I play the role of Yuri Fujisaki.
please remember me
Seriously, it's funny, everyone watch it.
It's seriously interesting.
Really cool.
No, thank you. I'm fine at my boss's level right now.
The actuation is also amazing!
It's a lot of action and a lot of beeswax.
And the open ending is really cool.
very good
Best for.
Seriously, it's funny.
I've already seen so many different works.
That's not good.
I was looking at something and I really...
Wait.
oh no (used as an expression of despair or when giving up)
this
ouch!
yay
Isn't this a bad idea?
amazing (e.g. of strength)
Hon.
The person himself/herself The person himself/herself
What?
Is it him?
such (about the actions of the listener, or about ideas expressed or understood by the listener)
I'm on the first day of Anime Japan.
Those on the second day...
See.
Isn't it bad that I'm in this lineup?
(sentence end) indicates emphasis, agreement, request for confirmation, etc.
You're promoting Nogizaka somehow.
Huh?
Nogizaka46 is a good group.
Oysters will write your name.
And two wills.
Yes, sir.
Packed.
They're all so cute.
that (something mentioned before which is distant psychologically or in terms of time)
Come and get me.
cute
Kyuuuu era (1154.10.28-1156.4.27)
amazed
Come here and you will be surrounded.
This place is amazing.
Ah, Inoshke.
Pseudobagrus ichikawai (species of catfish)
I'm not in the picture.
It's a great place.
I was the most excited one.
I'm a little tired. I'm out of breath.
white pig
cute
I love blue pigs.
And next door.
Mr. Takayama.
It's amazing you can come here.
I will definitely go to see it.
I'm going to see it, Mr. Takayama.
No, that's good.
That was fun.
I'm too excited.
I'm so excited.
Both sides listened to each other.
Both sides look animated.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
It's not good.
cool
amazing (e.g. of strength, effort, etc.)
Wow!
amazing (e.g. of strength)
Freelen Freelen
Freelen flowing.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
cute
It's like a movie theater.
Looks like a movie theater.
Wait. I don't like what I see from here.
cool
It's not good.
I want to take a picture, here.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
cool
The best of the best.
Moreover, both the floor and the course
Who are you pushing?
I like Yamaguchi-kun.
No, sir.
Yes, sir.
There's the ball.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
sunny place
Oh, my God.
I'll be the sun.
Well, I'll be Hinata.
OK
number of nights
I threw it.
Hey, I
Don't throw the kiichi either.
Kiichi threw it away too.
Because Kakki's guess.
What is Kakki's guess?
My guess?
Kakki's guess.
Come on.
I can't fly at all.
I like Yamaguchi.
It doesn't fly at all, not like this.
also
Here.
He said he jumped so hard.
Winner.
cute
Not flying at all.
Ten.
Oh, no.
Oh my God!
cute
Oh, that's not fair.
That's not fair. I'm caught between those two.
This is unfair.
No, no, I said that.
No, you can't.
What?
Don't say that.
Not you.
No, you can't.
What?
Don't say that.
Not you.
No, you can't.
Reverse.
What?
No, you can't.
I won't let you go.
This one is just to the left.
Insinuation.
No, sir.
He won't let go.
Oh, wow.
HirookaHirooka
It's true.
shugo (Kamakura or Muromachi period military governor)
You, stop.
Please do customer.
uh-huh
Fans on either side will be pissed.
never-ending
The Spy Family.
spy family
Spy Family Favorite
Do you like the Spy Family?
love (of)
I like it better than Beechnut.
Ah, the sword of swords.
The Sword of Swords
The character is the worst.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
My
By car
I want it.
It goes all the way up to the top.
absurdly large
Swords are a real lot of swords.
You know the type I like.
This is pretty much me.
Yes, sir.
Here you go.
swordsmith
how many swordsman?
There are a lot of swords Shiro.
Akita
useful tool
Really?
The boy on the fox's shoulders.
correct
I don't know how to read this.
such and such
Circle of my koma
It's not what it looks like.
It's hard to stand in line to buy goods and stuff in here.
Gong.
Griffings.
Gong's.
Imitation.
The new animation
Gong.
Killer, wait.
One more.
One more?
I'm definitely going to be a hunter.
Looks like.
I play like this.
It's true.
It was amazing, something that resonated right in the middle of my brain.
This is awesome.
welcome
I can't wait to go.
amazing
In here.
Someone's coming in.
How do I get in?
You want to come in?
A much bigger frog.
That's great.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
They're being eaten.
They ate me.
Nice picture.
Dungeon Meal
That's a dungeon meatball!
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
This is not a bad idea.
This is great, this is great, this is great.
We can go inside.
Come inside with me for a minute.
There's too many of them!
All the great characters.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
What an amazing view of the world!
The world view is awesome.
cool
Hey, Renca-chan, eat me, scorpion!
Will you eat?
Scorpions that can be eaten
old book
They'll eat it.
delicious-looking
I want to eat this.
This is absolutely delicious!
Insert shot.
what a surprise!
that extent
The ones that were violent.
So delicious!
It's now meat.
I hate it the most.
gah
This is great. This is great. This is great.
No, it's great, I like beautiful women.
Super cute. Very cute.
This is PicoMatch. I see.
Your love rules style is peachy.
cute
Oh, my God, we're so close. Can you play it?
Can you play it? The theater in Rizero.
Wow, wow, wow.
I'm sorry, this is called "summoning to another world" by any chance.
anger
Really?
This is great.
Great. This.
wonderful (e.g. of a meal)
Oh, Dokua.
dear
I miss this place.
That's what I'm trying to do to you.
I'm trying to make you feel special.
I'm happy to be treated special.
for the first time in one's life
Wow!
We're going to make it.
I almost hugged you for real during the process.
You got tears in your eyes?
I almost had a serious hug for a second.
I'll watch it again.
I'm your personal knight.
They'll reproduce it right away.
Cute~!
amazing (e.g. of strength)
He's shaking my hand.
Handshake could stay today.
Too cute!
Oh my God, what am I going to do?
I want to stay here forever.
super cute!
Cute~!
Maybe he's an angel?
Oh~
amazing (e.g. of strength)
Sign! Sign! Sign!
I did!
amazing (e.g. of strength)
This is awesome.
Oh, man.
Wait~
I've got a hell of a lot of stuff.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait!
Wait!
I don't know what to do!
Nagi!
They say you can take pictures.
Me first, Nagi.
I take a lot of pictures.
I like it.
Great.
very good
Thank you.
I like Nagi too.
May I?
cute
goitrous
Egoi good.
I like this one.
cute
conceited
Thank you.
I'm so happy for you.
I don't know what to do. I think I'll be the protagonist.
chicken grunt (species of fish, Parapristipoma trilineatum)
It's so cool.
It's a nice place.
It's cool.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
cute
overflying
It's firing so hard.
I love this uniform Nagi!
very strong
This is it.
This is bad.
I love wearing a punker with this uniform.
Looking forward to the movie
Let's watch a movie, shall we, ladies and gentlemen?
Let's all take a look.
dublive
Great. And wait, are you guys there?
I'm here a lot. We're all here.
I'm Kotori.
Oh, Kotori, yes.
I've been a first generation Kotori for a long time now.
this and that
Yes, yes, yes. Cute.
This is Kotoko.
cute
Wow, that's a lot.
So, Anime Japan 2024
I've been going around.
How did it go?
I had so much fun. I had so much fun.
It's not easy to have such a full day.
It was a dreamy space and a dreamy time.
I don't want to go home.
I don't want to go back.
You know, with my job and all.
I'm sorry it's hard for you to come to these events.
I'll do it, like this, even if it's just as a job.
They came to me like this.
And I'm allowed to go around like this.
It's really not that easy to find.
Thank you so much.
I don't know.
And if I could perform at your event, thank you.
It was fun It was fun It was fun
Thank you, everyone, for coming out.
actually
No, in this space.
We're on stage!
indignant
Really, the more I look at it, the more I see.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
If you thought this video was good...
Highly Rated Subscribe
please
see you later
Watch the cartoon.
Let's see a lot.
dildi divide
please remember me
Thank you for watching!